primelocation.com 2008-05-14

# privacy policy

The information collected about you by your use of the Primelocation.com website will be held by Primelocation.com, which is a trading style of Fastcrop plc, 2nd Floor, Hammersley House, 5-8 Warwick Street, London W1B 5LX.

You can use the Primelocation.com website without submitting your details but to get the most from the products and services available we may occasionally ask for personal information about you ("Personal Information") which we will endeavour to keep secure. We will process your Personal Information in the way indicated in this Privacy Policy.

Over time the way we process your Personal Information may change. We will let you know about changes that may not be obvious to you by publishing them in the Privacy Policy. By using the Primelocation.com website you agree to any change we tell you about unless, within 60 days of that notice, you write and tell us not to handle your information in the new way.

##### Marketing purposes

If you are a registered user, your Personal Information may be used by us and other businesses carefully selected by us to contact you in writing, by telephone or by e-mail ("Contact") to offer you content, advertisements, products and services that we believe may be of interest to you ("Marketing Purposes"). This may include personalised communications with you from Associated Newspapers and from other Daily Mail & General Trust group companies. You can opt out of receiving contact for Marketing Purposes any time by amending your registered details.

##### Automatically obtained data

We will automatically gather data such as your IP address, which site you had previously visited, the kind of browser you are using, and statistics about how you use the Primelocation.com website ("User Data"). The User Data will be linked to the Personal Information we hold about you to contact you for Marketing Purposes. We may share User Data in aggregated form with current or potential advertisers to allow them to present their advertisements more effectively.

##### Cookies

When you first visit our site we will automatically send you a cookie (a small text file which we create and send to your computer) which allows us to recognize you when you come back to the Primelocation.com website. If you wish to learn more, go to www.allaboutcookies.org. In addition to the cookies we send to your computer, some of our advertisers and third party ad servers will also send you their own cookies.

If you are concerned about cookies you have the ability through your browser to either reject all cookies or to provide a warning before any cookie is loaded on to your computer. If you decide to reject cookies you may find that you will not be able to take full advantage of some of the features and services in the Primelocation.com website. You may turn off cookies by following your browser's instructions. Detailed instructions are available at www.allaboutcookies.org.

##### View and/or amend your registered details

You can use your password to view and edit your registered details and the records we hold about you by clicking on "my Primelocation.com" on any page.

##### Access to your records

You have a right to see a copy of the information we hold about you if you pay us the fee set by law. If you wish to see a copy of the information we hold about you, please write to the Data Protection Officer, Fastcrop plc, 2nd Floor, Hammersley House, 5-8 Warwick Street, London W1B 5LX.

##### User initiated contact

If you contact us by telephone or by e-mail asking for assistance we will ask for or take your Personal Information. As well as using your Personal Information to help you, your Personal Information will be used to contact you for Marketing Purposes.

##### Prize draws

If you enter a prize draw, we will ask for your Personal Information which will be used to contact you for Marketing Purposes, whether you are the winner of the prize draw or not.

##### Property searches

You will be able to conduct a property search in the Primelocation.com website without giving us your Personal Information. However, if you wish to save properties to view at a later date we will ask you for your Personal Information, including your e-mail, which we will use to send you details of other properties you may be interested in. In addition, your Personal Information will be used to contact you for Marketing Purposes.

##### Application information

If you decide to apply for a service or buy a product provided by a third party who appears on the Primelocation.com website the third party will ask for details about you. That third party will pass your Personal Information to us. The Personal Information we receive from the third party will include data about your use of their service which will be used to contact you for Marketing Purposes.

Occasionally we will take application details for products or services provided by a third party who appears on the Primelocation.com website. We will pass this information to the third party to process your application and your Personal Information in the application details will also be used to contact you for Marketing Purposes.
